Miscellaneous literary manuscripts collection, 1958-1994
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
Miscellaneous literary manuscripts collection, 1958-1994
MS 355
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections.
Contains miscellaneous manuscripts of published and unpublished works, typescripts, page proofs, and some biographical material relating to the authors. The collection represents an artificial collation of manuscripts that have been donated or collected, but do not fit into other collections in the repository. Arranged alphabetically and by accession as received.
.75 linear ft.
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections University of Arizona PO Box 210055 Tucson, AZ 85721-0055 Phone: 520-621-6423 Fax: 520-621-9733 URL: http://speccoll.library.arizona.edu/
Restrictions
No restrictions.
Organization
This collection is organized into 1 series.
Series 1: Miscellaneous literary manuscripts, 1958-1994
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically and by accession as received.
Access Terms
Authors -- Manuscripts.
Bain, Willard S. -- Informed Sources.
Bishop, James, Jr. -- Epitaph for a Desert Anarchist.
Malanga, Gerard -- Biography.
The Divine Plan for Eileen.
Oates, Joyce Carol, 1938- -- The Sweet Enemy.
Oates, Joyce Carol, 1938- -- Sunday Dinner.
Oates, Joyce Carol, 1938- -- Ontological Proof of My Existence.
Sartre, Jean-Paul, 1905-1980 -- Freud.
Williams, Jonathan, 1929- -- Open Letter to Criticasters on the Occasion of three New Jargon Books.
Vonnegut, Kurt -- Jailbird.
Container List
- Series 1: Miscellaneous literary manuscripts collection, 1958-1994
  - Bain, Willard S. Informed Sources (Day East Received), 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bishop, James. Epitaph for a Desert Anarchist, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2-4)
  - Malanga, Gerard. The Divine Plan for Eileen, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Biographical information on Gerard Melanga no date (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol. The Sweet Enemy, ca. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol. Sunday Dinner, ca. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Oates, Joyce Carol. Ontological Proof of My Existence, ca. 1972 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sartre, Jean-Paul. Freud (original outline), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Williams, Jonathan. Open Letter to Criticasters on the Occasion of three New Jargon Books, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt. Jailbird (uncorrected page proof), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Vonnegut, Kurt. Jailbird (typescript with corrections and editorial notations), 1979 (Box 2, Folder 13-14)